[JESTER 10-A (M)]
The big day is coming!
Lord Aldarp's marriage!
[laughing]
[KAZUMA] Guess ole Aldarp
must be in a pretty big hurry.
'Cause it looks like
he's putting everything else
on hold to announce
the wedding date.
[indistinct chatter]
[MEGUMIN] This isn't the time
to be pouting, Kazuma!
[blowing]
[KAZUMA] Listen, I told you,
it was her decision.
And I'm not doing squat 'til
she comes crying for my help.
[growls]
- Hey!
- Sorry, I don't accept that!
If you're just going to wait
for that day and do nothing,
then I'll take action myself!
Go ahead, as long as it's not
too violent, all right?
And gimme that thing back.
You have no idea how long
I've been working on it.
[MEGUMIN]
Ahh.
What is this exactly?
[sighs]
See the bubbles?
You can pop 'em.
It relieves stress and it's
a lotta fun to play with, too.
Is that all it does?
[KAZUMA]
Uh-huh.
[grunts]
♪
[screams]
- [sighs]
- Oh, hey, uh...
I'm afraid this is quite
an urgent matter.
I've come here with a request,
Master Satou.
♪
[KAZUMA] Has Darkness finally
swallowed her pride
and admitted
that she needs my help?
What?
[MEGUMIN] "This warning
is for the Dustiness family.
A confidential source
has indicated that
one of the Devil King's
generals will be carrying out
an imminent attack on Axel's
chapel of the Eris Sect.
It has been scheduled
for the day of the wedding!
If the upcoming ceremony
is not canceled immediately,
the entire chapel
will be caught in a fiery blast
of Explosion magic!"
"For everybody's sake I hope
this letter is taken seriously
from a concerned wizard."
[KAZUMA]
I'm so sorry about this!
I'm gonna tear that
maniac a new one!
Megumin you better
get your butt out here!
And so, the days passed by
without Darkness.
I'd made up my mind about
letting the whole thing go
but the others...
[AQUA] Now, watch in amazement
as I pull a Rookie Slayer
out of this tiny little basket!
Don't pull crap like that
outta there!
Hey, what do you think
you're doing?
You need to let go of me,
all right?
Just take a look at all the
people who showed up
to see my awesome tricks!
[KAZUMA] Yeah, that's the
reason they called me here!
To do something about
the ruckus outside the house!
Hey, hurry it up
and do the trick!
[MAN 10-C (M)]
Right on with the show!
Please, I can't accept
donations from you.
I'm not a real entertainer,
so you can all just hold on
to your money, okay?
[AQUA] Kazuma this is all
a part of my master plan
to try and lure Darkness
out of her house.
- What?
- Yeah!
You know the legend
about the Amano-Iwato,
don't you, Kazuma?
- It's the same!
- [sighs]
[AQUA]
Yo, Darkness!
I know you're listening!
Hurry up and come out!
You're really gonna regret
not seeing this in person!
'Cause I'm gonna pull off
my best...
- [growls]
- Kazuma!
What the heck do you
think you're doing?
You better let go of me!
[KAZUMA]
We're heading home right now!
Wait you can't
drag me away, yet!
I've got more tricks!
I'm doing them every day
till she comes out!
[AQUA]
You hear me, Darkness?
Darkness!
[KAZUMA]
And a few days after that.
[groaning sigh]
Can't believe
I'm finally back here.
It's been three days, I think?
I already told ya,
you were gonna get arrested
for sending in those threats.
[thuds]
♪
[KAZUMA]
Just settle down, okay?
- 'Cause as far as I can tell...
- [slurps]
...all you and Aqua have done
is annoy the Dustiness Family.
♪
[MEGUMIN] In that case,
don't you think it's about time
you started helping out?
Uh!
Not until I hear something
from Darkness.
[thudding]
You're really awful!
The townspeople may
call you names like Kazutrash
and Crapuma
but, at the end of the day
I always thought you
were the kind of person
that would come through
for your friends
and lend a hand
when they need it the most.
[growling softly]
[sighs]
The man that I love
and care for.
He might complain
the whole time.
But when it really matters
I know he'd still come through.
That's what he's like.
♪
Lemme guess. You think
I'm just gonna roll over
if you throw in the word
"love," don't ya?
So sorry,
but I'm not that easy.
[scoffs]
[KAZUMA] Knock it off!
Ha, you know I'm ticklish.
[indistinct chatter]
[KAZUMA] Before long the day
of Darkness' wedding
finally arrived.
[blowing]
Let's get going, Kazuma!
It's about time
for us to crash a wedding!
[chuckles]
Uh-oh, a spell slipped
and the place was destroyed.
Oops, a spell slipped
and the lord's estate
was totally decimated!
Accidents happen!
[KAZUMA]
Don't do it, I'm serious.
It won't just end with debt.
You'd be a real criminal
this time around.
You'll regret
not going with me!
[KAZUMA]
Count me out.
[gasping]
[whimpering]
Come on, Kazuma!
So what that lord
might do to Darkness
doesn't even bother you?
Are you kidding me?
You don't care about her?
Of course, I do, damn it!
[gasps]
[KAZUMA]
How could I not care?
Uh-huh...
[sighs]
Maybe you haven't
heard about this
but that old creep
he'll do anything
to get his disgusting hands
on a woman.
And then when he's bored,
he just turns around
and throws 'em out.
The worst part is
he does this over and over.
Though, somehow, there's never
any evidence to prove it.
I can't stand that bastard!
♪
Then, you have to help!
At least try!
Surely you can come up
with some kind
of underhanded scheme!
♪
[KAZUMA] There's nothing
I can do this time.
This is a wedding
between two nobles
and there's tight security.
So, it would be impossible
for us to make any moves.
Our hands are tied on this one.
That's the reason
I've been waiting for Darkness
to reach out.
Kazuma.
Her Father's in bed
and really ill.
And we don't have
any connections
to other nobles here.
Fact is, I'm just a poor
adventuring loser.
[sighs]
♪
[KAZUMA] Chalk it up to our
different stations, I guess.
[sighs]
After all...
Darkness comes from
a different world than we do.
Just being able to go
adventuring with her
for so long
was basically a miracle.
♪
[sighs]
[footsteps]
♪
Kazuma you have been
thinking of ways to stop this.
I get it, now
and that's enough for me.
Huh?
That said I have
to think this through
and try to do what's best.
All right?
But, you should, too.
That way you can look back
and have no regrets.
♪
I'll leave you to it.
[door creaking opens]
[door closes]
♪
[KAZUMA]
It is what it is.
Hello there!
Your fickle "friends"
may have left you
but the all-seeing demon
has come to help!
Vanir?
You may feel it wise
to dance madly
while crying tears
of joy at my arrival!
Now then, why don't we
take a good look
at the fruits
of your knowledge?
Huh?
Do you seriously believe
I'm in any shape
to negotiate business with you?
I want to talk to that
pretty owner, right now!
That little debt-maker
couldn't negotiate
her way out of a paper bag.
Yesterday, she walks up
to me and says,
"This is going to be a massive
hit with adventurer couples!"
[VANIR] Then, she goes
and stocks this pendant!
What is that thing?
If the one who wears it
is ever fatally injured
then the last embers
of their life
ignite a rather
spectacular explosion!
[VANIR]
The concept is...
In your last remaining moments
you can draw your final breath
knowing you've protected
your beloved!
Isn't that the most
romantic thing ever?
Needless to say, she was
thrilled with the notion!
Yet the eruption is so volatile
that it blows away
not only the enemy,
but the beloved as well!
What better example
of the owner's "questionable"
entrepreneurial sense
could you ask for?
Care to make a purchase?
Nah, I'm good.
Hey, wait a minute you said
you're here to help me?
[VANIR]
Ohh!
I can see you've been
continuing product development,
as I so wisely advised.
Which brings me to...
♪
[gasps]
N-Now listen, Vanir,
these are the only ideas
that I've got left, okay?
And I won't let them go
for less than they're worth.
Such a paradoxical man.
You, the one who's desperate
to rescue the armored girl,
but feels terrified
by rejection!
The all-seeing Vanir
officially declares.
In exchange
for the intellectual rights
to your ideas
you will gladly accept
this incredibly
generous bag of money!
[laughs]
Now if you'll simply allow me
to verify the products
and rights involved.
Hey, listen, you know
all kinds of stuff, right?
Well, of course.
I can see just about anything.
For instance, I already have
the answer to the questions
you're about to ask me.
Huh.
[VANIR] Why in the world
is armor girl in debt
to this odious lord,
in the first place?
How is it, that despite his
rather vulgar appetites,
there's no evidence of that
man's debauchery whatsoever?
Hey, you're a demon, so--
[VANIR] "So why are you
trying to be so helpful
all of a sudden?"
"Are you plotting something?"
And, the answer to that is,
"most certainly."
I am a demon, after all.
But in this particular case
our interests are aligned.
So, I'm offering you
a helping hand.
How so?
Let's begin with the secret
ideas you've been saving
in case of an emergency.
I may well purchase them
at a discount on this day.
[KAZUMA]
Oh, man!
All-seeing demons
are the worst.
Anyway, if you really
have my answers,
could you stop holding out
and tell me, already?
Most assuredly.
Let me enlighten you!
Sacred Exorcism!
[laughter]
Whoa, you're
an archdemon, aren't ya?
How could you let
a plumbing Goddess do you in?
Huh, I leave you alone here
for five minutes
and now you're some
kinda demon worshiper?
And I'm a Water Goddess,
I'll have you know!
Do ya think you could
ever not butt in?
You were the one who left!
Hey, I was making sure
our guest was all right!
What are you even
talking about?
[KAZUMA] How could you...
The butler?
If you're preoccupied,
then I can just excuse myself.
Pardon me, sir, good day.
Oh, no, this is just...
[chuckles]
[VANIR] Devious attack
you thug of a Goddess!
Just look!
Do you see the crack
you've put on my amazing mask!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Think you could
ever forgive me?
I didn't realize I needed
to ask someone's permission
to exterminate a pest.
What are ya, stupid?
[snickering]
[KAZUMA]
Konosu Butt out?
[VANIR] Now then lad who finds
himself forsaken by the Gods,
despite his extreme proximity
to one of them.
Per our conversation
you were a bit curious
about the armor girl's
debt, yes?
[KAZUMA]
R-Right.
Interestingly...
the entire thing began
when you adventurers
brought down the
Mobile Fortress Destroyer.
The Destroyer?
♪
Go on.
When such a grand weapon
makes its presence felt
a lord's land is devastated.
[VANIR] That wasn't the case
in this town, however,
thanks to your
ludicrous struggles.
But isn't that a good thing?
[VANIR]
The town itself was spared
but there were myriad
of other concerns.
Such as the farmlands
surrounding it,
which were trampled
under the weight
of that eight-legged machine.
The ones who were tasked
with tending to those areas
effectively lost everything.
- Uh.
- And all of those peasants
turned to the lord of the land
in their time of need.
[groaning]
Quite right, it was exactly
as you'd imagine!
And what was
his chosen response?
[ALDARP] Consider the fact
that you survived at all
to be a victory.
But do be patient.
"Things will start
growing again, in time."
He said.
[both whimpering]
Ascribing the damage
to a natural disaster
didn't ease
their many troubles.
These people were desperate.
So, they came crying
to the Dustiness family,
with whom you're acquainted.
And this was their
impassioned plea.
[VANIR] Lord Dustiness,
who reimbursed damages
caused by the
adventurers' flooding!"
Tell us you'll find it
in your generous heart
to give us aid yet again.
We're begging you!"
-"Oh, please."
- [gasps]
Wait, what did you say?
Something about the
buildings damaged in the flood?
Mm-ha.
Remember back when you were
asked to pay for the damages
that your little group caused?
[VANIR] You weren't expected
to cover the costs, completely.
In fact, it was only
a portion, wasn't it?
Seems the Dustiness family
lost a majority
of their considerable wealth
paying for the destruction
the flood created.
[gasps]
And yet, despite that to aid
those whose livelihoods
were crushed by the Destroyer.
[VANIR]
They bowed to the local lord,
who shunned his own duties,
and borrowed the needed sum.
With one particular
stipulation.
♪
Now, if you have trouble
paying back the loan
for any reason whatsoever,
you can always use
your body as collateral.
[grunts]
[growling]
Oh, Kazuma.
Your hand must be in pain after
slamming the table like that.
I'm sure it's hurting you.
[KAZUMA]
That would explain everything.
How much money does
Darkness actually owe him?
[chuckles]
[VANIR] If we take the total
value of your personal assets
and add up the contents
of this bag,
it should just
about cover the cost.
Now then shall we discuss
our business?
[indistinct chatter]
♪
You look beautiful, Milady.
So lovely.
Once the wedding ceremony
is over,
I think you should visit
the master at the mansion.
Then, he'll be able
to see you in this dress
Hmm.
- [ALDARP] Move aside!
- [gasps]
In a matter of moments,
Lalatina will be mine.
Understand?
I do understand, sir,
but I'm afraid only members
of the Dustiness family
may enter.
I must ask you to leave.
You idiot!
Obviously, you don't seem
to realize that
after the nuptials,
I will be your employer!
That may be true
but, you can't pass
as I am not yet your employee.
[growls]
Well, I'll remember
your smug face!
Just you wait until
the wedding is over!
[sighs]
[DARKNESS] Could you please
call the guard for me?
I would like to thank him.
O-Of course.
[door creaking opens]
Come in.
Oh, Lady Dustiness.
You look so beautiful.
You refused him
and I thank you.
I will make certain
you are not punished for that.
You needn't worry.
I would've been quite
honored to serve any man
you had chosen, however.
A man that I had chosen, huh?
[chuckles]
If I may say, I feel
happy enough seeing you smiling
in light of the
current situation.
[footsteps]
And this may be rather
impertinent of me
but considering how
truly ravishing you are
engaging in such
frenzied personal play
may be a bad idea.
[door closes]
[whimpering]
This is his fault!
Kazuma and all those
ridiculous impersonations!
[sighs]
♪
[DARKNESS] While there may be
a few exceptions
most people
who are born to nobility
are never really able to live
life as they would like.
But, in spite of that
I was so fortunate
as I spent the majority
of my time around those
with whom I could be myself.
And that is enough.
Asking for any more
would only be selfish.
Now it is my turn to repay
the people of this town.
♪
[MAID 10-A (F)]
Milady?
Oh, sorry.
Forgive me.
[DARKNESS] I wonder how the
others in our group would react
if they ever found out
about my debt.
Megumin would be furious.
Aqua would start crying out
of nowhere, more than likely.
And as for him, he would
probably call me an idiot,
then give an unbelievably
long lecture
while harassing me
with pinpoint accuracy
before trying something
to save me.
♪
Will he come here today?
No, certainly not.
Knowing him, he is holed up
in the mansion, sulking,
with a sour look on his face.
Hmm.
[knocking]
[HAGEN]
It's time to begin, Milady.
The priest presiding
over the ceremony
is one who's very
well respected
and from what I understand,
the finest in town.
I'm quite certain this will be
a wonderful occasion.
♪
[DARKNESS] I had such
an unforgettable time.
Truly, this year with the
others has been very special.
[light background chatter]
[DARKNESS] Every day was
so much fun and so joyful.
[light background chatter]
[sighs]
[indistinct chatter]
[SAKAMAKI]
Quit shoving, damn it!
I still can't see inside!
[indistinct chatter]
I just want you to know,
I'll be praying
for your happiness, Milady.
Hmm.
♪
Hmm. Ooh!
[evil chuckle]
♪
Ahh, well...
you Darkness, are here today,
to take this old man,
who looks just like a cross
between a pig and a bear.
- [gasps]
- A pig?
[AQUA (PRIEST)] In keeping
with the laws laid down
by some other God, not me
and being pressured into a
marriage against your own will.
In sickness and in health,
in good times and bad,
for richer and for poorer.
Will you love this old man?
Honor this old man?
Treasure this old man?
- Aid this old man?
- [indistinct chatter]
Cherish this old man?
Tend to this old man?
And adore this old man
for the rest of your days,
- until death do you part?
- [whimpering]
I'm not an old man!
Of course, you can't do that.
So, I say we should leave here
and head home,
then chow down on the food
Kazuma made for us!
After that, we'll all sit
around and drink bubbly!
[all gasping]
Wait, I know you!
You're the same woman who came
to my luxurious mansion
and made a complete mess of it!
[gasps]
♪
[KAZUMA]
Hi, Dad. Hi, Mom.
I just wanted to let you know
your adorable son
who you raised to be
a pretty normal boy
is about to say "goodbye"
to all of that now.
[AQUA]
Go, Kazuma get her!
[KAZUMA] Considering
I'm picking' a fight
with the biggest
bigshot around here,
not to mention kidnapping
a noble lady!
[gasps]
Let's go home, Darkness!
[GROUP]
Dear Devil King!
- [HANS] We!
- [VERDIA] We!
[SYLVIA]
All of us!
[GROUP] Will enjoy living
on the banks of the river Styx!
[SYLVIA]
And endeavor to continue...